Thanks for coming by.
謝謝你們趕過來
We wanted to bounce some ideas off of you about the wedding ceremony.
我們希望你們能幫我們 想一些婚禮上用的點子
-What's the matter? Are you okay? -It's just...
-怎麼了？你還好嗎？ -那只是因為…
Monica said "wedding."
摩妮卡說了「婚禮」
We thought one of you could read something.
我們希望你們之中 有人能上台念些感性的文章
Okay, yeah, I guess I can do that too.
好吧，我想我應該也能勝任
Too?
也能勝任？
I kind of have something else planned for you guys.
我自己想了一個點子 來慶祝你們的婚禮
-Do you mind telling us what it is? -Sorry.
-你能告訴我們是什麼點子嗎？ -抱歉
I'm kind of keeping this one on the QT.
我想把它當成是高度機密
Whatever it is, I hope it involves winking.
不管你是指哪個，我希望會有眨眼睛
-Hey. -Hey.
-嘿 -嘿
I talked to one of the DOOL writers..
我跟DOOL的編劇談過…
-What is DOOL? -Days Of Our Lives.
-什麼是DOOL？ -《我們的日子》
You won't believe it. My character is coming out of his coma!
你們一定不相信 我演的角色就要醒過來了
-That's wonderful. -Wow, Joey.
-那真的是太棒了 -哇，喬伊
And not only that. I'm getting a new brain!
不只是那個，我會有個新腦子！
So great things are happening at work and in your personal life.
你的工作跟私生活 都有了很棒的進展
You're getting a new brain?
你要換個新腦子？
They're killing off one of the characters...
他們要踢走劇中一個角色…
and her brain is being transplanted into my body.
將她的腦子移植到我的身體裡
What? A brain transplant?
什麼？腦部移植手術？
It's ridiculous.
這太可笑了
It's ridiculous that you haven't had sex in three months.
可笑的是你三個半月沒有做過愛
It's winter. There are fewer people on the street.
現在是冬天，街上的人少了很多
Who are they killing off?
他們要踢走誰？
Cecilia Monroe. She plays Jessica Lockhart.
西西雅夢露，她飾演潔西卡拉哈特
No!
不！
She is so good at throwing drinks in people's faces.
她最擅長將飲料潑到別人臉上
I don't think I've ever seen her finish a drink.
我從來沒看過她喝完一杯飲料
The way she slaps people. Wouldn't you love to?
還有她打人巴掌的樣子 你不想那麼做嗎？
Don't do it.
別那麼做
And she's been on the show forever.
她參與這齣戲的演出很久了
It's gonna be really hard to fill her shoes.
要代替她一定很難
Help me out here.
你得幫幫我
When you come out of the brain transplant...
當你做過腦部移植手術後…
you are going to be her?
你要變成她？
Yes, but in Drake Ramoray's body.
對，她被困在德瑞克的身體裡
Why is this so hard for you to get? I thought you were a scientist.
你為什麼就是搞不懂？ 我還以為你是科學家
The One Where Joey Gets A New Brain
本集播出：喬伊的新腦袋
rainystar壓制iPod-MP4
Rach, so that guy there:
瑞秋，那邊那個男的…
Straight or gay?
是異性戀還是同性戀？
Oh, yeah, he's too cute to be straight.
他太帥了，不可能是異性戀
Knockers will help us figure it out.
大波霸小姐會幫我們查個清楚
All right, straight.
好了，他是異性戀
And not subtle.
而且一眼就看得出來
He left his cell phone.
他忘了拿手機
We could have Gunther put it in lost and found.
我們得把它交給阿甘 放在失物招領處
Or we could use it to call China, see how those guys are doing.
或是用它打電話到中國 看看那些人在做什麼
What if he calls his own cell phone and I answer...
如果他打電話來找手機 我接了電話…
and we start talking and we fell in love?
我們開始聊天，之後墜入愛河呢？
Would that be a great story?
那是個很棒的故事吧？
Kind of like a fairy tale for the digital age.
就像是數位時代的童話故事
That does sound great. I'm getting the phone.
那聽起來很棒，我要去拿手機
What? Wait. Why do you get the story?
什麼？等一下 為什麼你會成為故事的女主角？
I haven't been out on a date in so long.
我已經很久沒有約會了
Phoebe, you had a date three days ago.
菲比，三天前你才約過會
That wasn't a date. That was friends getting together and having sex.
那不是約會，那只是 朋友聚會，然後做愛
Okay. Great. I get the phone.
好吧，我去拿手機
No way. You just broke up with Tag a week ago.
不行，一星期前你才跟泰格分手
Yeah, and until now, I didn't think I would love again.
對，直到現在，我才明白 我能再愛一次
-Nice try. -Wait.
-說的好 -等一下
How do we fairly decide who gets the phone?
我們該怎麼公平地決定 誰能拿走手機呢？
I don't know.
我不知道
Maybe we could...
或許我們可以…
Ah-ha! Too slow!
你動作太慢了！
Ah-ha! Too cocky.
你太自大了
（銀杯片廠）
I'm dating him. There's nothing you can do.
我在跟他約會，你管不了
Yes, there is.
不，我管得了
Are you going to kill him like you did Charles?
你打算怎麼做？殺了他嗎？ 就像你殺了查爾斯？
Oh, my baby.
我的寶貝
Cut!
卡！
That was great. And that slap looked so real. How do you do that?
你演得太好了，剛剛那一巴掌 很逼真，你怎麼辦到的？
-Oh, just years of experience. -Can I get some ice here?!
-那只是多年的經驗 -快拿冰塊過來給我
I just wanted to say how wonderful I think you are.
我只想說我覺得你的演技很棒
You're not the fan who's dying,  are you?
你該不會是那個快死掉的影迷吧？
I'm Joey Tribbiani. We did a scene together yesterday.
我是喬伊崔比亞尼 昨天我們合拍過一場戲
-I'm the guy in the coma. -Oh, that was a real person?
-我就是那個昏迷的人 -那是真人？
Since I'm getting your brain when you leave the show...
因為你離開後我要移植你的腦子…
I was wondering if..
我在想如果…
-I'm leaving the show? -Why? Did you hear something?
-我要離開？ -為什麼？你聽到了什麼？
Who told you that?
是誰告訴你的？
-One of the writers. -Was it bald or was it tall?
-編劇之一 -哪個編劇？是禿頭佬還是高個子？
You know, it doesn't matter,  because it is not true.
那不重要，因為那不是真的
Okay.
好吧
And if it were true, how dare you come to me and ask me for tips...
如果那是真的 你竟然敢來叫我教你…
about a character I've played for 20 years!
該如何飾演我演了二十年的角色
Miss Monroe.. Oh, there you go.
夢露小姐…喔，你真的那麼做了
Okay, look, I have an idea.
好吧，聽著，我有個點子
Why don't we see what kind of numbers he has on his speed dial...
我們為什麼不看看 他的速撥鍵記錄了哪些電話號碼…
and then whoever has more in common with him gets the phone.
跟他有最多共通點的人 就可以把手機拿走
-Fine. All right. -All right.
-好吧 -好吧
First name on the speed dial is "Mom."
速撥鍵的第一個名字是「媽媽」
Oh. I lost my mom to suicide.
喔，我媽媽自殺死了
You can't use that to get the cute guy and the last blueberry muffin.
不行，你不能利用那一點 搶走帥哥跟最後一塊藍莓鬆餅
Did I use that already today? Sorry.
今天我已經用過那個借口了？對不起
"Ben, Carlos, David.."
班，卡洛斯，大衛…
Oh, I win. He's got Barney's on his speed dial.
我贏了，他在速撥鍵裡記下了巴尼斯
You don't know it's Barney's the store.
你不知道他指的是不是巴尼斯服飾店
That could be his friend's house, a bar..
那可能是他朋友家或是酒吧的電話…
Who has Barney's the store on their speed dial?
誰會把巴尼斯服飾店的電話 記錄成速撥鍵？
His new girlfriend.
他的新女朋友
What is that?
那是什麼聲音？
I think it's the Dying Cat Parade.
我想是快死掉的貓在舉行遊行
Sounds like it's coming from across the street.
聽起來是從對街傳來的
-Oh, my God. -What?
-我的天啊 -什麼？
The thing that Ross was gonna do at our wedding?
還記得羅斯說他要在 婚禮上給我們驚喜嗎？
He was hanging out with me and said,  "You're half Scottish, right?"
他跟我出去混時說： 「你有蘇格蘭的血統吧？」
No. There is no way. It cannot be Ross.
不，不可能，不可能是羅斯
Unbelievable. Why is your family Scottish?
不可思議，為什麼你有蘇格蘭血統？
Why is your family Ross?
為什麼羅斯是你哥哥？
He cannot play at our wedding.
他不能在婚禮上演奏 大家都會跑光的
I mean, come on. That is just noise!
我是說那只是噪音！
It's not even a song.
那根本不算是歌
Wait. If you listen very carefully...
等一下，如果你仔細聽…
I think it's "Celebration" by Kool and the Gang.
我想它是庫爾 與夥伴合唱團唱的《慶祝》
You're right. They are writing me out of the show.
你說的對，他們要將我踢出這齣戲
They don't know exactly when it's going to happen, but soon...
他們還沒有決定 什麼時候，但應該很快…
and then that's it.
就是這樣了
If it was up to me,  you would never leave the show.
我真的很抱歉，如果我可以決定 你永遠都不會離開這齣戲
-Yeah, thanks. -I mean it.
-謝謝你 -我是認真的
I can't believe they'd do this to you. And to your fans.
我不敢相信他們會對你這麼做 還有你的影迷
They're gonna be devastated. Heartbroken. They love you so much.
他們一定會崩潰傷心 他們是那麼地愛你
Oh, you're right.
你說的對
Thank you.
謝謝
What's your name again?
你說你叫什麼名字？
-Joey. -Thank you.
-喬伊 -謝謝你
That is so sweet.
那真的太貼心了
The only reason I came up to you before...
聽著，之前我會來找你...
is because, well...
是因為…
I'm really nervous about being you.
因為要飾演你我真的很緊張
If you could help me capture the essence of the character...
請你幫我抓住角色的精髓
Help me keep Jessica alive. Please?
幫助我讓潔西卡 繼續活下去，可以嗎？
Joey, I will help you.
好吧，喬伊，我會幫你
Not because I owe it to this stupid show...
不是因為我對這出蠢戲有虧欠…
but because I owe it to Jessica.
而是因為我虧欠潔西卡
-Oh, thank you so much. -You're so welcome.
-那真的是太棒了，謝謝你 -別客氣
I've been watching some tapes. How's this?
我一直在觀摩錄影帶 你覺得這招如何？
Jessica Lockhart will never step foot in this place again!
潔西卡拉哈特 永遠都不會再踏入這裡！
Never!
永遠都不會！
Jessica doesn't have an English accent.
但潔西卡沒有英國腔
I can do an English accent?
我有英國腔？
That baby's going on my resume.
我要把這點寫在我的履歷表裡
-Hi. How are you? -Good.
-嗨，你好嗎？ -我很好
Remember when we were in the coffeehouse...
還記得我們在咖啡廳時…
we decided I was gonna keep the cute guy's phone?
我們決定我可以 拿走那個帥哥的手機嗎？
I was gonna keep it in my purse, so if it rang, I could just pick it up?
我要把它放在我的皮包裡 如果它響了，我就能立刻接聽？
Do you remember going into my purse and stealing the phone?
你還記得你從我的皮包 把手機偷走了嗎？
Ooh, now you lost me.
我聽不懂你在說什麼
-You stole the phone. -No, I didn't.
-你偷走了手機 -不，我沒有
You're saying if I called it,  it wouldn't ring?
如果我撥號過去它不會響嗎？
-No. -Okay.
-不會 -好吧
But while you dial, let me show you the features of my new ringing handbag.
既然你要撥號了，我要讓你看看 我剛買的響鈴皮包
Oh, it does work.
喔，它真的有用
-Phoebe. -That is a different phone.
-菲比 -那是另一隻手機
Oh, is it? Hello. Yes, hi. Is Rachel there?
是嗎？喂，對，你好，瑞秋在嗎？
Yes, she is. Just one moment, please. It's for me!
她在，請稍等，是找我的！
That is damning evidence.
那是鐵證
Oh, my God. I bet that's him.
我的天啊，我敢說是他打來的
My digital fairy tale's about to begin.
我的數位童話故事就要開始了
Would you stop doing that?
你能不能別再那麼做了？
Hello? Yes, I'm the one who found your phone.
喂，對，我就是撿到你手機的人
-Phoebe, you can't.. -Shh, I'm on a call.
-菲比，你不能… -我在講電話
Yeah, you can pick it up tonight. Say,8:30?
對，今晚你能過來拿，就八點半吧？
At my apartment.
到我家來
It's 5 Morton Street, apartment 14.
摩頓街五號，十四號房
And then maybe, you know, after, we can grab a bite to eat or whatever.
或許之後我們可以去吃點東西
Okay. Okay, I'll see you then. Bye.
好的，到時候見，再見
I will be here when he comes over.
你知道他來的時候我會在這裡
How will you know what time to come over?
你怎麼知道他什麼時候會來？
You just said it.
你剛剛說出來了
Oh.
The essence of the character is rooted in her confidence.
這個角色的精髓源自於她的自信
So when Jessica enters a room, for instance...
譬如說，當潔西卡走進一個房間時…
she owns everything...
她擁有那個房間裡…
and every person in that room.
所有事物跟所有人
-You try it. -Okay.
-你來試試看 -好吧
He's not mad at the room.
他沒有對這個房間生氣
Try it again. He owns it. He owns the room.
再試一次，他擁有它 他擁有這個房間
It is his. He owns, owns, owns the room! He owns it!
這是他的，他擁有 這個房間！他擁有它！
It's a little weird, but it's getting better.
這有點奇怪，但已經好多了
I'm gonna miss this woman so much. I don't know what I'm gonna do.
我一定會很想念這個女人 我不知道我該怎麼辦
It's been 20 years of my life.
我演這齣戲二十年了
Hey, hey. Maybe this is a good thing.
或許這是件好事
It'll give you a chance to shake things up. Play different characters.
它給你機會做改變 扮演不一樣的角色
You're so talented.
你才華洋溢
Probably should've just left years ago when the offers were pouring in...
或許我該在幾年前離開 那時很多人要我接戲…
but I just got so comfy here and...
但我在這裡過得太舒服…
I turned down some amazing work.
我拒絕了一些大好機會
Like what?
譬如說呢？
Well, let's just say if I'd left 15 years ago...
喔，就說如果我在十五年前離開…
the landscape of Mexican cinema would be very different today.
現在的墨西哥影壇會完全不一樣
Wow.
哇
But, well, now... Now's a different time for me.
但現在…現在時機不一樣了
Oh, hey, come on. Don't do this.
嘿，別這樣
Let me tell you something, okay?
聽我說句話，好嗎？
When I watch you do a scene, I'm thinking, "She is a great actress."
當我看到你演戲時 我想「天啊，她是個很棒的演員」
But I'm also thinking, "She is hot."
但我也會想「她好辣」
You think I'm hot?
你覺得我很辣？
You own the room.
你擁有這個房間
We should probably get the...
或許我們應該…
Oh, yeah. Yeah, we should get..
對，我們應該…
So when Jessica kisses a man...
當潔西卡吻男人時…
she usually puts...
她通常會把…
both her hands on the man's face.
雙手放在那個男人臉上
I notice that. Is that because she's so passionate?
我注意到了，那是因為她 充滿了熱情嗎？
No, it's because that way the camera only sees her.
不，那是因為 那樣子攝影機只能拍到她
You want to try it?
你想試試看嗎？
Yeah, okay.
好的
That was good. That was really good.
太棒了，真的很不錯
But I think that maybe your hands are just a little off. They should..
但我想你手的位置不對 它們應該…
Well, I feel like a snack.
我想吃點點心
Do you want some shortbread? It's Scottish, like you are.
你要吃點脆餅嗎？ 它是你故鄉蘇格蘭的點心
Oh, no, thanks. I don't like anything from my Scottish heritage.
不，謝謝，我不喜歡蘇格蘭的東西
What?
什麼？
Well, it's just that my entire family was run out of Scotland by...
因為我的家族被趕出蘇格蘭…
Vikings.
是維京人幹的
It sounds like your family's ready to rediscover its Scottish roots.
聽起來你家人 準備要恢復蘇格蘭傳統
You can't play bagpipes at the wedding!
你不能在婚禮上吹風笛！
How did you know?
你們怎麼知道？
-We heard you play from our apartment. -Were you the ones who called the cops?
-我們聽到你在家裡吹風笛 -是你們去報警的？
That's not really important right now.
現在那真的不重要
What is important is, while we appreciate the gesture...
重要的是，我們謝謝你的好意…
we just don't feel that bagpipes are appropriate for our wedding.
我們只是覺得 我們的婚禮上不適合吹風笛
-Why not? -Because we hate them.
-為什麼？ -因為我們討厭風笛
Just give me a chance to perform for you, then decide whatever you want.
給我機會為你們表演 再做最後的決定
I'm not gonna tell you what song I'm gonna play, either.
我也不會告訴你們 我要吹哪首曲子
Let's just say when it's over...
就說當表演結束後…
I'll bet there'll be a wee bit o'celebration.
我們一定會慶祝一下
Hey, hey!
嘿！
Who is it?
是誰？
It's Tom. I'm here to pick up the phone.
我是湯姆，我來拿手機的
Why do you get to answer the door?
為什麼要由你去開門？
-Why shouldn't I? -Because it's my apartment.
-為什麼不行？ -因為這裡是我家
Then I get to give him the phone.
那麼由我來把手機交給他
Okay. Good luck explaining all the calls to China.
好吧，希望你能好好 跟他解釋那些打到中國的電話
Hi.
嗨
Wow, how long were we arguing for?
我們爭執了多久？
You're not the man who left the phone.
你不是那個忘了拿手機的人
-No, that's my assistant. -Is he coming?
-對，他是我的助理 -他會來嗎？
No.
不會
-Could you give us one second? -Sure.
-你能讓我們談一下嗎？ -沒問題
We'll be right back, sir.
我們馬上回來
-What do we do? -I don't know.
-我們該怎麼辦？ -我不知道
Can you believe this?
你能相信嗎？
We were waiting for a hot guy and a hotter one shows up.
我們在等一個帥哥 結果來了一個超級大帥哥
I know..
我知道
What?
什麼？
Rachel, listen...
瑞秋，聽我說…
if you let me have him, then I will really owe you one.
如果你能把他讓給我 我真的欠你一個大人情
All right.
好吧
All right, I will let you have him.
好吧，我把他讓給你
But you owe me. You owe me big.
但你欠我一個大人情
Which one of you will I take to dinner?
哪一位漂亮的小姐要陪我去吃晚餐？
Oh, that'd be me, sir.
是我
-你先請 -謝謝
Nice.
太棒了
Well, you certainly own that room.
你的確擁有那個房間
Actually, I rent the whole place. I just got what you meant. Thank you.
事實上我租下整間公寓 我剛瞭解你的意思，謝謝誇獎
-Hi. -Hey.
-嗨 -嘿
Oh, my God.
我的天啊
Oh, Jessica Lockhart! In my apartment!
潔西卡拉哈特！在我家裡面！
I am such a huge fan. I am such a huge fan.
我是你的頭號大影迷 我是你的頭號大影迷
It's nice to know..
很高興能知道…
Monica!
摩妮卡！
That's my roommate, Rachel.
她是我的室友瑞秋
That explains the women's underwear.
難怪你家會有女人內衣
Sure.
沒錯
Oh, my God, it's true!
我的天啊，是真的！
Can I just ask you to do me just one favor?
我的天啊，我能請你幫我一個忙嗎？
Certainly.
當然可以
Would you slap me right here in the face?
你能打我一巴掌嗎？
I'd love to, but my lawyer said I can't do that anymore.
我很願意，但我的律師說 我不能再那麼做了
All right, here we go.
好了，我們走吧
No, wait. Just one moment.
不，等一下，還有一件事
-You're a stupid bitch. -I really can't slap you.
-你是個笨女人 -我真的不能打你巴掌
-My God, you're great. -Thanks for stopping by.
-我的天啊，你太棒了 -謝謝你們過來
-I am so sorry about that. -Oh, no.
-我真的很抱歉 -不
Being adored, I'm used to it. Don't worry about it.
我習慣被影迷包圍，別擔心
-Oh, my God. -What?
-我的天啊 -什麼？
They sent me today's script. They never send me the script.
他們寄了今天的劇本來給我 他們從來沒有寄劇本給過我
-They don't? -I'm in a coma.
-是嗎？ -我一直都昏迷不醒
This must mean I have lines.
這代表我有台詞了
Oh.
How does it happen?
我是怎麼死的？
You get thrown from a horse into an electric fence.
你摔下馬，然後撞到電籬笆
A what? Jessica hates horses.
什麼？潔西卡討厭馬
After this she's not gonna be crazy about electricity, either.
經過這件事，她也不會喜歡電
Loosening the saddle on Mother's horse was brilliant, Fredrick.
在媽媽的馬鞍上動手腳 是個超級好點子，佛萊德克
And the electric fence, inspired.
電籬笆那個點子太妙了
Thank you, sweetheart.
謝謝你，親愛的
I can't believe she's really gone.
我不敢相信她真的死了
Look around you. All of this is ours.
看看你的四周，一切都是你的
I don't think so.
我可不那麼認為
Who are you?
你是誰？
What's the matter, Dina?
怎麼了？笛娜
Don't you recognize your own...
你不認得你自己的…
mother?
媽媽嗎？
Cut! That was great, everybody. Thank you.
卡！大家都演得很好，謝謝
That was so wonderful!
那真的是太棒了
I think that you're a better Jessica than I ever was.
我想你比我更適合演潔西卡
-Oh, no. -Of course not, but you were good.
-喔，不 -當然不是，但你真的很棒
Thanks.
謝謝
Good news. I got another job.
好消息，我找到新工作了
Great. Hey, all right! What is it?
太棒了，是什麼樣的工作
A film in Guadalajara.
我要到瓜達拉哈拉拍電影
The airport?
你是指那個機場？
No, that's LaGuardia.
不，那是拉瓜迪亞機場
-This is Mexico. -Oh, wow.
-我要去墨西哥 -哇
Well, how long will you be gone?
你會去多久？
Eight months.
八個月
-That's a really long time. -Yeah, but you could come and visit.
-那真的很久 -對，但你可以來看我
I bet you could own a few places down there.
我敢說你能在那裡擁有幾個地方
Oh, you know, I should probably buy a place in the city first.
你知道的，或許我該先在紐約買房子
And I just got what you meant. That is..
我剛瞭解你的意思，那…
-That's a tricky one. -It's tricky.
-那真的有難度 -真的很難
Good luck.
祝你好運
You too.
你也是
Now, remember, I'm still learning.
請記住 我還在學吹風笛
One, two, three, four!
一，二，三，四！
You know this song. Sing along.
你們都知道這首歌，一起唱吧
So?
怎麼樣？
No!
-不 -不